olist.ng 2019-12-04

# OList Nigeria | Free Online Marketplace to Buy & Sell

PRIVACY POLICY

Your privacy is important to us which is why we have developed the OList Privacy Policy. It will help you understand how we collect, use, disclose and use personal information. 

BY USING THE SERVICE, YOU PROMISE US THAT (I) YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREED TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND (II) YOU ARE OVER 18 YEARS OF AGE (OR HAVE HAD YOUR PARENT OR GUARDIAN READ AND AGREED TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR YOU). If you do not agree or are unable to make this promise, you must not use the service. In such case, you must contact the support team via online chat or email to request a deletion of your account and data.

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECTED

Data that you need to submit to us

You may be asked to provide us information about yourself when you register for and/or use the service. This information includes but not limited to first name, phone number, email, last name, photo, address details, etc. 

Additional information may be needed sometimes in order to fulfill your other requests such as restore your account or when you participate in a promotional campaign on our website. We may share your data with third parties in certain circumstances. We may, for example, share data with:

  1. 1)government bodies and law enforcement agencies, to comply with the law;
  2. 2)professional advisers, to enforce or defend our legal rights; or
  3. 3)with a purchaser or seller in connection with a corporate event such as a merger, business acquisition or insolvency situation.

Data provided to us by third parties

When you decide to log in using Facebook or Google, we get personal data from your Facebook or Google account according to your consent. We also may get more information about your Ads from other third parties.

Data protection statement

Information will be filtered out according to its purpose.

We will collect and use personal information solely to fulfill the purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We will make readily available to customers, information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business under these principles to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Privacy Policy Changes

These Terms may be modified without notice at any time in the future. Changes will be posted on our website. It is your responsibility to remain informed of any changes as you are bound by the latest version of the Privacy Policy.

Data Retention 

We will store your personal data for as long as it is reasonably necessary for achieving the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy (including providing the service to you), which includes (but is not limited to) the period during which you have an OList account. We will also retain and use your personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

DATA TRANSFER

We are a part of an international group of companies with data-centers around the world, your data may be transferred to other countries including countries which do not have the same level of data protection laws as those in the country where you are located. We will, however, ensure that your data is protected to a strict standard
